Oh my God.
I desperately need to get some Botox.
Well. Xavi can give you Botox. Can't he?
Ugh. Xavi's been really getting
on my nerves. I swear to God.
What's wrong?
I'm pretty sure that he's getting hit on
by that trashy girl in class.
Oh God…
And… you know how men are.
They just can't resist. can they?
But it's no big deal.
I've got a little back-up plan
I'm working on. so…
-But… I mean. you're still together?
-Obviously.
Xavi and I are supposed to be together.
We can't live without each other.
We're the perfect couple.
Aww.
Ugh. my wrinkles.
Oh. Marissa! Look who's here!
-Ugh.
-It's our little vampire queen.
Listen. could we chat for a sec?
Sure. Samantha.
You know. we admire you a lot.
It's impressive… just how much
you don't seem to care about. uh.
existing in darkness.
Uh. thanks? I suppose.
Mm.
Can I leave? Please?
You're so dark and misunderstood.
You're the kind of person who gets
a smidge of admiration
once you're buried in a morgue.
And Samantha thought…
Well. I guess what everybody's thinking…
It would be amazing
if you killed yourself.
Think it over.
Did you steal that line
from a horror flick? Or…?
Well. maybe. But don't you think
it's at least kind of a good idea?
Whatever.
Y'know what I think?
You're all moody
'cause you've got a big secret.
Like what?
Oh. nothing.
I mean. just what happened between you
and your teacher at your old school.
God. wouldn't it be awful
if everybody found out?
-Aw!
-Oh c'mon. Don't worry about it.
I'm very discreet.
Buh-bye!
FINAL PROJECT
-Hey. Why are you here?
-The principal wants to talk. so…
-So. what? Did you get detention?
-No. um… not at all.
All right. See ya around.
Okay. you got me.
I have to stay
'cause I got in trouble today.
-Because…?
-Because…
I kinda dumped a ton of paint on Samantha.
Well. I mean.
she probably had it coming. right?
Hey. "a woman has to live her life.
or live to repent not having lived it."
Didn't you know?
"But I do live my life."
I didn't think you got to that part.
It's from the beginning of the novel.
Don't try to pretend we're super close.
We're two classmates
doing a project together. okay?
Then why'd you bother
to tell me about why you got detention?
Huh?
-Good luck with your match. though.
-Thanks.
Yo. dude.
Can't wait to tell you
about this stream idea.
Oh. really? What's the idea?
Nah. bruh. I can't tell ya.
I can't explain it.
You gotta see it in person.
Okay. Lookin' forward to it.
You're sorta like my manager. Pato.
No. dude. C'mon. we've talked about this.
I'm not your manager. Xavi.
We're business partners. Okay?
-Got it? You and me are the same.
-Got it. Whatever you say.
Are you still throwing
a party this weekend?
Oh. yeah. This Friday.
-Bet. I'll explain it at the party.
-Okay.
Let's just say that the vampire
is about to get caught
in the jaw of a wolf.
See ya.
LADY CHATTERLEY'S LOVER
What are you doing here?
I got detention.
Why? What happened out there?
I got a little revenge on someone.
Revenge on who?
Hey. don't forget.
we're just two classmates
doing a project together. okay?
You don't need the details.
Here. I got you this.
For when you go to London.
Javi. you didn't have to.
You think it's cringey. Okay. it's fine.
-No big deal.
-No.
I love it. I promise.
I just… feel a little embarrassed
accepting it.
Uh. so… how long do we stay here?
Normally. it goes till 5:00.
but sometimes we get
to leave a little before that.
Okay. I'll let my mom know when to get me.
Y'know. if you want.
I'd be more than happy to drive you.
Seriously?
Just say yes.
It's no trouble. really. I have a car.
Hey. Ma? I've got a ride. okay?
That's why I'm trying to move out.
Don't wanna keep living with my parents.
Yeah. I get it.
Sometimes I wish I could move somewhere
super far from here. Really far away.
Yeah.
Well. thank you for driving me. Xavi.
It means a lot to me.
No worries.
-So. see you tomorrow? Or…?
-Mm-hmm.
Cool.
Tell me. tell me. love
Ooh. what have I done?
Sorry. is this enough…
No. Xavi.
Sorry.
Hold me…
You know what?
I'm not sorry.
I'm not apologizing for that.
Will you hold me?
Your love was strong
Oh. your love was strong
Xavi. let's stop.
Let's stop and be friends. okay?
Nothing more.
I can't keep hiding how I feel about you.
Are you telling me
you don't feel the same way?
That you don't want this?
No. I'm not. I have feelings for you.
But I'm a bit…
So what? Why can't we be together. then?
I'm scared about what could happen.
Seriously. you have a girlfriend. Xavi.
I'm nobody. The trashy "Vampire Queen."
according to Samantha.
Samantha is such a terrible person.
If you hate her that much.
why are you with her?
It's too complicated to explain.
Well.
then this is too complicated.
-Thanks again for driving me. Xavi.
-Tamara! Tamara. please.
Tamara!
Whoa. you're always on my mind
When you've been served a lie
But still. they're number one
I am new to being around
Alone in the crowd
It's you and me tonight
I swear that I don't let go
When you tell me how I told you so
Show me just a new pose
I feel it in your heartbeat
I feel it. I feel it in you
Subtitle translation by: Meredith Cannella